(this.webpackJsonpquiz1=this.webpackJsonpquiz1||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,i,t){},14:function(e,i,t){"use strict";t.r(i);var o=t(0),r=t.n(o),c=t(2),s=t.n(c),a=t(6),n=t(3),h=t(4),d=t(7),l=t(5),u=(t(13),[{id:0,question:"In what year did William the Conquerer begin the Norman Conquest of Great Britain?",answerChoices:[{id:"0a",choice:"1863 AD",isCorrect:!1},{id:"0b",choice:"1066 AD",isCorrect:!0},{id:"0c",choice:"1776 AD",isCorrect:!1},{id:"0d",choice:"44 BC",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:1,question:"What landmark science fiction novel by Frank Herbert was credited as a major influence on the Star Wars films?",answerChoices:[{id:"1a",choice:"Foundation",isCorrect:!1},{id:"1b",choice:"Dune",isCorrect:!0},{id:"1c",choice:"Stranger in a Strange Land",isCorrect:!1},{id:"1d",choice:"Childhood's End",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:2,question:"After Julius Caesar's murder by members of the Senate, who succeeded him as the ruler of Rome?",answerChoices:[{id:"2a",choice:"Julia",isCorrect:!1},{id:"2b",choice:"Caesarion",isCorrect:!1},{id:"2c",choice:"Octavian",isCorrect:!0},{id:"2d",choice:"Gaius",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:3,question:'What 1988 debut album by the Pixies featured the songs "Gigantic" and "Where Is My Mind?"',answerChoices:[{id:"3a",choice:"Doolittle",isCorrect:!1},{id:"3b",choice:"Trompe le Monde",isCorrect:!1},{id:"3c",choice:"Bossanova",isCorrect:!1},{id:"3d",choice:"Surfer Rosa",isCorrect:!0}]},{id:4,question:"Which of these colleges is not a member of the Ivy League?",answerChoices:[{id:"4a",choice:"Providence College",isCorrect:!0},{id:"4b",choice:"University of Pennsylvania",isCorrect:!1},{id:"4c",choice:"Princeton",isCorrect:!1},{id:"4d",choice:"Yale",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:5,question:"At which of these fictional schools did Peter Parker attend high school?",answerChoices:[{id:"5a",choice:"Coal Hill School",isCorrect:!1},{id:"5b",choice:"Rydell High School",isCorrect:!1},{id:"5c",choice:"Midtown High School",isCorrect:!0},{id:"5d",choice:"Ditko High School",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:6,question:"Which of these women has not served as Secretary of State?",answerChoices:[{id:"6a",choice:"Hillary Clinton",isCorrect:!1},{id:"6b",choice:"Janet Reno",isCorrect:!0},{id:"6c",choice:"Condoleeza Rice",isCorrect:!1},{id:"6d",choice:"Madeleine Albright",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:7,question:"During most of his NBA career, Michael Jordan wore the number 23. What other number did he briefly wear?",answerChoices:[{id:"7a",choice:"45",isCorrect:!0},{id:"7b",choice:"11",isCorrect:!1},{id:"7c",choice:"32",isCorrect:!1},{id:"7d",choice:"42",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:8,question:"Who assasinated Archduke Franz Ferdinand of Austria, setting in motion the events leading to World War I?",answerChoices:[{id:"8a",choice:"Sirhan Sirhan",isCorrect:!1},{id:"8b",choice:"Nathuram Godse",isCorrect:!1},{id:"8c",choice:"Leon Czolgosz",isCorrect:!1},{id:"8d",choice:"Gavrilo Princip",isCorrect:!0}]},{id:9,question:"The Marvel character Matt Murdock (Daredevil) was abandoned by his mother as an infant. He encountered her years later in her capacity as a what?",answerChoices:[{id:"9a",choice:"Social worker",isCorrect:!1},{id:"9b",choice:"Nun",isCorrect:!0},{id:"9c",choice:"Police officer",isCorrect:!1},{id:"9d",choice:"Lawyer",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:10,question:'The books "The Talisman" and "Black House" follow the adventures of Jack Sawyer. What author did Stephen King collaborate with on both novels?',answerChoices:[{id:"10a",choice:"Peter Straub",isCorrect:!0},{id:"10b",choice:"Joe Lansdale",isCorrect:!1},{id:"10c",choice:"Richard Chizmar",isCorrect:!1},{id:"10d",choice:"Joe Hill",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:11,question:'What author wrote the travel memoir "Travels with Charley: In Search of America?" ',answerChoices:[{id:"11a",choice:"Jack Kerouac",isCorrect:!1},{id:"11b",choice:"John Steinbeck",isCorrect:!0},{id:"11c",choice:"Ernest Hemingway",isCorrect:!1},{id:"11d",choice:"Mark Twain",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:12,question:"The Victorian British novelist Mary Ann Evans wrote under what male pen name?",answerChoices:[{id:"12a",choice:"George Eliot",isCorrect:!0},{id:"12b",choice:"George Sand",isCorrect:!1},{id:"12c",choice:"Michael Field",isCorrect:!1},{id:"12d",choice:"Magnus Flyte",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:13,question:"BBC journalist and The Guardian columnist Ben Hammersley is credited with coining what modern tech term?",answerChoices:[{id:"13a",choice:"Selfie",isCorrect:!1},{id:"13b",choice:"Podcast",isCorrect:!0},{id:"13c",choice:"Streaming",isCorrect:!1},{id:"13d",choice:"Emoji",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:14,question:"There are currently how many elements listed on the Periodic Table of Elements?",answerChoices:[{id:"14a",choice:"108",isCorrect:!1},{id:"14b",choice:"115",isCorrect:!1},{id:"14c",choice:"118",isCorrect:!0},{id:"14d",choice:"92",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:15,question:'What modernist poet was known for poems such as "The Waste Lands" and "The Hollow Men"?',answerChoices:[{id:"15a",choice:"Ezra Pound",isCorrect:!1},{id:"15b",choice:"T.S. Eliot",isCorrect:!0},{id:"15c",choice:"William Carlos Williams",isCorrect:!1},{id:"15d",choice:"Carl Sandburg",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:16,question:"Lew Alcindor is a legendary athlete better known by what name?",answerChoices:[{id:"16a",choice:"Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",isCorrect:!0},{id:"16b",choice:"Muhammad Ali",isCorrect:!1},{id:"16c",choice:"Metta World Peace",isCorrect:!1},{id:"16d",choice:"Sugar Ray Robinson",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:17,question:"Who is credited with the invention of the World Wide Web?",answerChoices:[{id:"17a",choice:"Al Gore",isCorrect:!1},{id:"17b",choice:"Alan Turing",isCorrect:!1},{id:"17c",choice:"Steve Wozniak",isCorrect:!1},{id:"17d",choice:"Tim Berners-Lee",isCorrect:!0}]},{id:18,question:"Who was credited with killing Billy the Kid?",answerChoices:[{id:"18a",choice:"William H. Bonney",isCorrect:!1},{id:"18b",choice:"Pat Garrett",isCorrect:!0},{id:"18c",choice:"Henry McCarty",isCorrect:!1},{id:"18d",choice:"Ollie P. Roberts",isCorrect:!1}]},{id:19,question:"Jonas Salk is known for developing the first vaccine for what virus?",answerChoices:[{id:"19a",choice:"Smallpox",isCorrect:!1},{id:"19b",choice:"Flu",isCorrect:!1},{id:"19c",choice:"Measles",isCorrect:!1},{id:"19d",choice:"Polio",isCorrect:!0}]}]),C=function(e){var i="";return"intro"===e.quizStage?i="Do you have what it takes to ace the legendary general knowledge quiz?":"playing"===e.quizStage?i=e.currentQuestion.question:"end"===e.quizStage&&(i="Congratulations. You finished. "),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-area"},r.a.createElement("h2",{className:"question"},i))},m=function(e){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:e.className,id:e.id})},g=function(e){for(var i="",t={visibility:i=e.inProgress?"visible":"hidden"},o=function(t){var o="progress-bar";return t<e.questionCount||"end"===e.quizStage?o+=" answered":o+=" not-answered",r.a.createElement(m,{key:t,id:t,className:o,style:i})},c=[],s=0;s<20;s++)c.push(o(s));return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress",style:t},r.a.createElement("h4",{className:"progress-text",style:t},"Question ",e.questionCount+1," of 20"),c)},b=function(e){return r.a.createElement("button",{className:"choice",onClick:function(){e.clickStart()}},"Start")},w=function(e){return r.a.createElement("button",{className:"choice",id:e.id,onClick:function(i){e.isCorrect?i.target.className="correct":i.target.className="incorrect",setTimeout((function(){return e.nextQuestion(e.isCorrect)}),1e3)}},e.choice)},f=function(e){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"score"},r.a.createElement("h1",{className:"score-text"},"You got ",e.score/20*100,"% correct. "),r.a.createElement("h2",{className:"burn"},function(e){var i="";return 0===e?i="Captain, we are detecting no signs of intelligent life.":e<=5?i="Ah, jeez...no. Just no.":e>5&&e<=10?i="I mean, it's pretty bad. Could be worse, but not by much.":e>10&&e<=15?i="I wouldn't say you are a complete moron.":e>15&&e<=19?i="Maybe there is hope for humanity. Not bad.":20===e&&(i="Okay. I'm impressed. You are a legend. Well done."),i}(e.score)),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"choice",onClick:function(){e.reset()}},"Try Again"))},q=function(e){for(var i=e.length-1;i>0;i--){var t=Math.floor(Math.random()*i),o=e[i];e[i]=e[t],e[t]=o}return e},S=function(e){var i;if("intro"===e.quizStage)i=r.a.createElement(b,{clickStart:e.clickStart});else if("playing"===e.quizStage){i=q(e.choices).map((function(i){return r.a.createElement(w,{choice:i.choice,key:i.id,id:i.id,isCorrect:i.isCorrect,nextQuestion:e.nextQuestion})}))}else i=r.a.createElement(f,{score:e.score,reset:e.reset});return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-area"},i)},y={questionSet:[{id:0,question:"",answerChoices:[{id:"",choice:"",isCorrect:!1},{id:"",choice:"",isCorrect:!0},{id:"",choice:"",isCorrect:!1},{id:"",choice:"",isCorrect:!1}]}],questionCount:0,inProgress:!1,quizStage:"intro",score:0},v=function(e){Object(d.a)(t,e);var i=Object(l.a)(t);function t(e){var o;return Object(n.a)(this,t),(o=i.call(this)).clickStart=function(){var e=q(u);o.setState({questionSet:e,inProgress:!0,quizStage:"playing"})},o.nextQuestion=function(e){var i=o.state.score,t=o.state.questionCount+1,r="playing";e&&i++,20===t&&(r="end",t--),o.setState({score:i,questionCount:t,quizStage:r})},o.reset=function(){o.setState(Object(a.a)({},o.state=y))},o.state=y,o}return Object(h.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},r.a.createElement(C,{quizStage:this.state.quizStage,currentQuestion:this.state.questionSet[this.state.questionCount],questionCount:this.state.questionCount}),r.a.createElement(S,{quizStage:this.state.quizStage,questionCount:this.state.questionCount,clickStart:this.clickStart,choices:this.state.questionSet[this.state.questionCount].answerChoices,nextQuestion:this.nextQuestion,score:this.state.score,reset:this.reset}),r.a.createElement(g,{inProgress:this.state.inProgress,questionCount:this.state.questionCount,quizStage:this.state.quizStage})))}}]),t}(o.Component);s.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(v,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},8:function(e,i,t){e.exports=t(14)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2b1c6bc8.chunk.js.map